<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>SimWrapper Blog</title>
        <link>https://simwrapper.github.io/blog</link>
        <description>The best place to stay up-to-date with the latest SimWrapper news and events.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 06:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <image>
            <title>SimWrapper Blog</title>
            <url>https://simwrapper.github.io/img/SW_favicon.png</url>
            <link>https://simwrapper.github.io/blog</link>
        </image>
        <copyright>Copyright © 2022 VSP, TU Berlin</copyright>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ActivitySim and SimWrapper]]></title>
            <link>https://simwrapper.github.io/blog/2021/11/15/activitysim.html</link>
            <guid>https://simwrapper.github.io/blog/2021/11/15/activitysim.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Please welcome <a href="https://activitysim.github.io">ActivitySim</a> to the SimWrapper family!</p> <p>ActivitySim is an advanced activity-based transport model being co-developed by a consortium of cities and state agencies in the U.S. There is now an ActivitySim flavor of SimWrapper being implemen...</p>]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using SimWrapper with local files on your PC/laptop]]></title>
            <link>https://simwrapper.github.io/blog/2021/01/27/local-files.html</link>
            <guid>https://simwrapper.github.io/blog/2021/01/27/local-files.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>You don't need to set up any external file servers or upload outputs to subversion to use SimWrapper: you can explore the files stored on your own laptop right away.</p>
<p>This is great for debugging runs and for files that you cannot make public (or that you don't want to make public just yet).</p>
<p>All you need to do is run the <strong>Mini File Server</strong> program on your local machine, in the folder that you want SimWrapper to have access to. It is a simple HTTP web server that lets your browser access that folder (and only that folder) via <code>localhost:8000</code>. Your machine's default firewall will prevent any outside network or internet access.</p>
<p>Here's how to set it up.</p>
]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome to SimWrapper 👋]]></title>
            <link>https://simwrapper.github.io/blog/2021/01/15/hello.html</link>
            <guid>https://simwrapper.github.io/blog/2021/01/15/hello.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>New documentation site! I'm excited to get this info &quot;out there&quot;, in the hopes that more people will find SimWrapper useful after reading these pages.</p> <p>Let me know if you see mistakes or have suggestions on what topics need to be added. Ther...</p>]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>